An 81 -year -old man ended up in Germany by accident after trying to get from
Newcastle, Great Britain, to Rome, Italy.
The old -age pensioner was on a mission to see the Pope, who is head of the Catholic
Church, and decided to make his way there by car.
He was surprised when his GPS system told him he had arrived, although there were no
signs of any of the famous buildings or architecture.
signs of any of the famous buildings or
He was surprised when his GPS system told him he had arrived, although there were no
signs of any of the famous buildings or architecture.
The man parked but didn't put on the handbrake of his car properly.
His car rolled backwards, and in a striking display of irony, hit a sign saying,
Rome. The man parked but didn't put on the handbrake of his car properly.
The man parked but didn't put on the handbrake of his car properly.
His car rolled backwards, and in a striking display of irony, hit a saying, Rome.
The small town in North Germany he had mistakenly plugged into the GPS system.
Police said that the car had come to a halt after hitting the sign.